slingbox.com 2015-06-27

# Slingbox.com - Sling Media Privacy Policy

**Introduction:**

Sling Media, Inc. ("Sling Media") respects your privacy. This Privacy Policy applies to all of our websites, mobile applications and our other products and services (collectively, "Slingbox Products"). This Privacy Policy explains what information we collect through the Slingbox Products, how we use that information, who we share that information with and what choices you have to limit or prevent the collection of your information.

The Slingbox Products may contain links to other companies or individual's websites, platforms, devices or services. This Privacy Policy does not apply to, and Sling Media is not responsible for: (i) the practices of any other companies or individuals, or (ii) any third party websites, platforms, devices or services that you link to from the Slingbox Products. You are responsible for reviewing the privacy policies of any other websites, platforms, devices or services that you connect to from the Slingbox Products.

Please take a few moments to read this Privacy Policy. By accessing the Slingbox Products, you agree to accept the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and are aware that our policies may evolve in the future as indicated below. In the event of a conflict between this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, our Terms of Use will control.

**What information we collect:**

In various places in connection with Slingbox Products, we collect "Personally Identifiable Information," such as your name, postal address, telephone number, email address, payment information or other information that can be used to identify you or contact you. For example, we may collect this information when you sign up for our email newsletter, purchase or register a Slingbox Product, register for a "Slingbox Account", enter a sweepstakes or participate in promotions and giveaways. From time to time in the future we may offer additional features, services and promotional opportunities that would require you to submit Personally Identifiable Information to participate.

We also collect "Anonymous Information" including, your IP address, your ZIP code, geolocation data, your Media Access Control (MAC) address, your SlingFinder ID, the name you assigned to your Slingbox Product, the hardware and firmware version of your Slingbox Product, the type of browser you use, the websites that you visit, the identity of your television or video content provider, the content you view, the search terms that you enter, the advertisements that you click and the number and frequency of users of Slingbox Products. Anonymous Information will not be associated with Personally Identifiable Information.

Like many technology companies and service providers, we also use "cookies" to collect and store information about your activities on a website or other platform. A cookie is a small data file that stores separate files within your web browser. When you visit websites or other platforms the cookie identifies your computer (or other devices for accessing the Internet) to us so that you do not have to re-register each time you visit. We and certain of our third party partners use cookies to enhance the Slingbox Products, compile aggregate data about your programming choices, display targeted advertisements based on your activities, measure the traffic to our site and its different services and features, and other miscellaneous uses. If you choose to do so, you can configure your web browser to delete existing cookies or disable cookies altogether. However, certain features of the Slingbox Products may not work if you delete or disable cookies.

We do not intend that children will use the Slingbox Products. We do not solicit or knowingly collect information from children under 13 years old, nor will we knowingly accept registration from them.

**How we use the information we collect:**

We use Personally Identifiable Information that you provide us for such purposes as responding to your requests for information, products or services, customizing the advertising and content you see, and communicating with you about our offerings. For example, if you sign up for our email newsletter, we will send the newsletter to the email address you provided. If you so choose, we will also use Personally Identifiable Information to send you information about products and services that may be of interest to you. Later on in this Privacy Policy, we provide you with more information on what choices you have.

We use Anonymous Information to determine how people use the Slingbox Products. For example this data tells us information including how often users click on our advertisements, which files are downloaded most frequently, and which components or areas of Slingbox Products are the most popular. Analyzing this data allows us to improve the offerings on and performance of Slingbox Products.

**How we share information:**

We sometimes use third parties to help with some aspects of the Slingbox Products, such as delivering content, processing payments and providing marketing assistance. When we supply Personally Identifiable Information to these third parties, we require them to use it only for the function they are helping us with.

We aggregate the Anonymous Information that we collect and exchange it with advertisers and other partners who are interested in the use and performance of the Slingbox Products. We share this type of data so that our partners also may provide you with an optimal user experience and better understand how users access the Slingbox Products.

We will disclose Personally Identifiable Information as required by law, or if in our judgment it is necessary to protect Sling Media or our employees or users from harm, loss or liability. If we merge with or are acquired by another company or we sell substantially all of our assets, the acquiror or resulting company will receive and may continue to use the information you have provided as described in this Privacy Policy. In the unlikely event we cease operation or enter bankruptcy, your information may be transferred to and used by another company that acquires our assets or offers similar or related products or services. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any such acquiror or successor may continue to use your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

Third party advertising on Slingbox Products

Information shared with advertisers. Sling Media may share the information collected from or about you in aggregated and other non-personally identifiable forms with advertisers and our business partners in order to tailor advertisements, measure advertising effectiveness, and enable other enhancements. This information includes your use of the Slingbox Products, websites you visited, advertisements you viewed, programming choices and your other online activities.

Clicking on or viewing ads. When you click on or view an advertisement via a Slingbox Product, the third party advertiser or our business partners may collect some information from or about you. The information practices of these third parties are governed by their own privacy policies and are not covered by this Privacy Policy. Please be aware that Sling Media does not warn you when you have chosen to click through to another website or platform when using the Slingbox Products. We recommend that you familiarize yourself with the privacy policies of such other websites or platforms to determine how they handle any information they separately collect from you.

Personally Identifiable Information you can access:

We allow you to access the following information about you for the purpose of viewing, and in certain situations, updating that information. This list will change as Slingbox Products change. You may currently access the following information:

  * user profile, and
  * user preferences.

**What choices you have:**

When you register for the Slingbox Products, you have the option of checking a box to tell us that you do not want us to send you any information about our products and services, or that you do not want to receive information from our partners and others about products and services that might interest you. We will keep track of your decision in our database. Even if you choose not to receive information from us, we reserve the right to communicate with you on matters we consider especially important. Further, please note that if you do not want to receive legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Policy, those legal notices will still govern your use of the Slingbox Products, and you are responsible for reviewing such legal notices for changes.

You are able to add or update certain information on pages, such as those listed in the "Personally Identifiable Information you can access" section above. When you update information, however, we often maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records.

You may delete your account at any time by calling Sling Media's customer support line at (877) 467-5464. Please note that some information may remain in our records after deletion of your account.

Notice to California residents:

Do Not Track ("DNT"). DNT is a privacy preference that users may set in certain web browsers that sends a signal to websites and services that they do not want certain information about their website visits collected over time and across websites. Like many other online service providers, Sling Media does not currently alter its data collection practices when it receives DNT signals because there is no consensus among industry participants as to what DNT means in this context. To find out more about DNT, you may visit [http://www.allaboutdnt.com](http://www.allaboutdnt.com/).

**Postings:**

If you use our bulletin boards, post user comments regarding content available through the Slingbox Products, or engage in similar activity, please remember that anything you post is publicly available. Portions of your user profile will also be available to other users of our websites.

**Security:**

During sessions in which you give us information such as credit card numbers, we encrypt your transmissions using SSL ("Secure Sockets Layer"), and other security technology. We keep the Personally Identifiable Information you provide us on servers that are protected by firewalls and other technological means against intrusion or unauthorized access. They are located in a physically secure facility; however, there is no such thing as "perfect security" on the Internet. We rely on you to select passwords that cannot be guessed easily and to safeguard those passwords from disclosure. By using the Slingbox Products you acknowledge that we cannot guarantee the information you transmit to us will be 100% secure. Your use of the Slingbox Products and information you provide us is at your own risk. Please contact us if you have any information regarding unauthorized use of the Slingbox Products.

**Consent to Transfer:**

If you are located in the European Union, Mexico, Canada or elsewhere outside of the United States, please be aware that information we collect will be transferred to and processed in the United States. By using the Slingbox Products, or providing us with any information, you hereby authorize and consent to this transfer, processing and storage of your information in the United States, a jurisdiction in which the privacy laws may not be as comprehensive as those in the country where you reside or are a citizen.

Changes to this Privacy Statement:

We may make changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time for any reason. Use of information we have collected or collect about you is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used (though you always have the option to delete your account as described above). If we make changes in the way we use Personally Identifiable Information, we will notify you via e-mail or by posting an announcement on our website. The latest version will be available at http://www.slingbox.com/get/privacy-policy. You will be bound by any changes to this Privacy Policy when you use Slingbox Products after receiving notice of such changes.

Effective Date: The Effective Date of this Privacy Statement is January 1, 2015.
